howhot.io 2019-07-12

# Privacy Policy - Merantix

**Last updated May 21, 2018.**

**INFORMATION WE COLLECT**

Through this Website we may collect “Non-Personal Information” and “Personal Information.” Non-Personal Information includes information that cannot be used to personally identify you, such as your IP address, anonymous usage data, general demographic information, preferences you submit and preferences that are generated based on the data you submit. Personal Information includes information that can be linked to a specific individual, such as a name, address, phone number, payment information, email address, login information for third party sites and other information which you submit to us through the Website. 

**Information You Provide Us**

In order to create an account (“Account”) or use the Website, you must be at least 18 years of age. When you create an Account or use the Website, we may ask you to provide us the following information: first and last name, email address, mailing address, gender and country of residence. You may also be asked to provide job application information if you are interested in joining the team.

**Information Collected by the Website**

We may collect information about the mobile device or computer you use to access the Website, including without limitation the hardware model, operating system and version, browser type, network information, IP address and your approximate geographic location via IP geolocation.

We may use text files called persistent cookies to help us better understand user behavior by telling us which parts of our Website people have visited, which enables us to improve the usability, performance and effectiveness of the Website.

We also use Google Analytics, which includes a tracking token, and may use other technologies in the future, for similar purposes. These monitoring tools collect information anonymously and report website trends to us without identifying individual visitors. This information can be combined with the information you have generated and transmitted to or through us or provided to us, which will enable us to analyze and improve the Website. Google’s ability to use and share information collected by Google Analytics about your visits to the Website is restricted by the Google Analytics Terms of Service and the Google Privacy Policy. If you prefer to not have data reported by Google Analytics, you can install the Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on available [here](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout). 

**Our Policies Concerning Children**

The Website is not intended for use by children under 13 years of age. If we become aware that a child under 13 years of age or anyone else under the age of 18 has provided us with Personal Information, we will delete that information and the associated Account.

**HOW WE USE AND SHARE YOUR INFORMATION**

**Personal Information**

Personal Information you provide to us is used to help us communicate with you and to provide you with the Website. For example, we may use Personal Information to: (i) register and service your Account, (ii) process your job application, (iii) solicit feedback and respond to your questions, and (iv) provide technical support.

We do not sell, lease, rent or otherwise disclose or transfer your Personal Information to any third party, except as otherwise set out in this Privacy Policy.

We may disclose your information as follows: 

  * Third party service providers: we may, from time to time, outsource some or all of the operations of our business to third party service providers or partner with third parties for special projects or initiatives, including the development of new products or services. We provide such third parties with the minimum amount of information needed for the purpose of accomplishing their tasks, and have mechanisms in place to ensure that such third parties maintain the confidentiality and security of the information we provide them.
  * Legal Investigations and requests: we may disclose your information to law enforcement agencies or other governmental agencies when required to do so or when, in good faith, we believe it is necessary in order to comply with legal obligations.

**Non-Personal Information**

We use Non-Personal Information to help us analyze and improve the Website and may also aggregate Non-Personal Information in order to track trends and analyze use patterns on the Website. This Privacy Policy does not limit in any way our use our disclosure of Non-Personal Information and we reserve the right to use and disclose such Non-Personal Information to our partners and other third parties at our discretion (including aggregated and/or anonymized information about our users and their use of the Website).

**Mergers, Acquisitions and Similar Business Transactions**

In the event we undergo a business transaction such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of all or a portion of our assets, or in the event of our bankruptcy or insolvency, your Personal Information as well as Non-Personal Information may be among the assets transferred to a third party. You acknowledge and consent that such transfers may occur and are permitted by this Privacy Policy, and that any acquirer of our assets may continue to process your Personal Information as set forth in this Privacy Policy. 

**Data Retention**

We may retain your information for as long as is necessary to provide you with the Website. If you wish to delete information we have collected, please contact us at any time by email via team@merantix.com.

**YOUR PREFERENCES**

If you don’t want to receive any emails that are not necessary to ensure the regular operation of your Account or the availability of the Website, you can email us at team@merantix.com. You can stop using the Website at any time, but note that your information may be retained as described above.

**DATA SECURITY**

The Company and our service providers implement security measures designed to protect your information from unauthorized access, disclosure or accidental loss or destruction of Non-Personal Information and Personal Information. We utilize appropriate physical, technical and managerial safeguards designed to protect the information we collect from or about our users. The Company’s physical infrastructure is currently hosted and managed by GoDaddy Inc., 14455 North Hayden Road Scottsdale, AZ 85260, United States 

**INTERNATIONAL USERS**

The Website is hosted and operated in Germany and the United States. If you reside outside the United States, your information will be transferred to, processed and stored in the United States under U.S. privacy standards. By using the Website and providing information to us, you consent to such transfer and processing of your information by the Company.

**CHANGES TO OUR PRIVACY POLICY**

We may occasionally update this Privacy Policy. When we do update this Privacy Policy, we will revise the “Last Updated” date of the Policy. If we make changes to this Privacy Policy that, in our discretion, we consider significant, we will post the updated Privacy Policy on the Website and we may also send emails to our users who have created an Account containing a link to the revised Privacy Policy. Please review this Privacy Policy periodically to stay informed about how we are protecting the Personal Information we collect. If you continue to use the Website after we post an update to this Privacy Policy, you indicate your acceptance of the updated Privacy Policy.

**CONTACT US**

If you wish to access, delete or correct your information, or have any additional questions regarding this Privacy Policy or the Website, please contact us by email via team@merantix.com.

————————————————————————————————–

## **ADD ON MX HEALTHCARE GMBH**

**Website data protection statement and information for data subjects pursuant to Article 13 and Article 14 of the EU General Data Protection Regulation**

**General Information about the controller**

Company:  MX Healthcare GmbH  
Legal representative: Jonas Muff  
Address: Friedrichstr. 125, 10117 Berlin, Germany

**Data Protection Officer / Datenschutzbeauftragter**

c/o activeMind AG Management- und Technologieberatung  
Kurfürstendamm 56  
10707 Berlin  
Tel.: +49 (0)30 / 770 19 10 760  
Email: datenschutz.healthcare@merantix.com

**General data processing information**

Personal data is only collected if communicated to us. Apart from that, no personal data is collected. Any processing of your personal data that goes beyond the scope of the statutory permission is only possible on the basis of your express consent.

_Processing purpose II  _Contract execution.  
_Categories of recipients II  _External service providers or other contractors. Other external bodies in so far as the data subject has given consent or transmission is permitted due to a prevailing interest.  
_Third-country transfers II  _As part of contractual execution, processors could also be located outside the European Union.  
_Duration of data storage II  _The duration of data storage depends on the statutory storage requirements and is usually 10 years.

**Specific information about the website**

**_Use of Google Analytics_**

This website uses Google Analytics, a web analytics service provided by Google Inc. (“Google”). Google Analytics uses so-called “cookies,” text files that are stored on your computer and that allow an analysis of your use of the website. The information generated by the cookie about your use of this website is usually transmitted to a Google server in the US and stored there. However, in the event IP anonymization is activated on this website, your IP address will be shortened beforehand by Google within member states of the European Union or in other signatory states to the Treaty on the European Economic Area. The full IP address will be transmitted to a Google server in the USA and shortened there only on an exceptional basis. Google will use this information for the purpose of evaluating your use of the website, compiling reports on website activity for website operators, and providing other services to website operators relating to website activity and Internet usage. Google will not associate the IP address transmitted under Google Analytics by your browser with other data held by Google. You may prevent the storage of cookies by selecting the appropriate settings on your browser software; however, we should inform you in this case that you might not be able to enjoy all of the functionality of this website to its full extent. You may additionally prevent the recording of the data (including your IP address) to Google that is generated by the cookie and that pertains to your use of the website, or the processing of these data, by downloading and installing the following browser plug-in available through the following link:  [http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=de](http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=de).

**Further information and contacts**

In addition, you may invoke your rights to correction or deletion at any time, to restrict processing, to object to processing and data portability. You also have the right to contact the data protection supervisory authority for complaints.
